The world is awash in pain.
Now, wars are fought between spies
over information -
in shadow wars.
We've got this.
The target's eyes haven't adjusted
to the darkness yet!
Today is the day, Teach!
We're finally going to make you admit defeat!
SPY CLASSROOM
MISSION: Flower Garden II
It all started five days ago...
Defeat me.
Make me say, "I surrender."
You can use whatever methods you like.
Come up with plans as a group,
and take me down by the end of the month.
That concludes the lesson.
So, what was that about?
Ah, I see.
It will be a simulation of actual combat conditions.
We could dig up dirt.
Physically restrain him.
Take his friends or loved ones hostage.
In the world of espionage, spies are often asked
to manipulate and cajole their targets.
I suspect that's what this training is about.
He said we could use whatever
methods we liked, right?
That's what I heard too, yo!
That's all well and good, but...
It was Klaus, right?
Feels like that guy...
...thinks we're a fuckin' joke!
Like he can walk all over us,
just 'cuz we're washouts!
Come on, everyone.
I'm sure that's not what he-
Well, I say we teach him a lesson
and show him just how strong we are.
Yeah!
Seven against one will hardly make for decent training.
We can just win by sheer numbers!
Let's all go attack him together!
Are there any more complaints about my lesson plan?
No, sir.
Good.
Next time, make sure to actually use your heads.
That marked the start of our radical new
Defeat Teach curriculum, but...
For the next five days,
all we did was rack up one loss after another.
We've got this.
The target's eyes haven't adjusted
to the darkness yet!
Today is the day, Teach!
We're finally going to make you admit defeat!
Hope you're-
Hope you're read-
Damn it, Lily!
Hey! Keep your hands to yourself!
I ain't touchin' shit!
It's not my fault your tits are so damn big.
S-settle down. The target has no clothes, let alone a weapon.
Magnificent.
By my count, that makes thirteen attempts.
I applaud your tenacity.
That said, your plans still need work.
When you attack someone, you need to be
as sharp as a wind racing through a valley.
At least put on a towel!
There's no need.
A first-rate spy thinks nothing of
being seen in the nude.
I'm heading out.
I'll return tonight.
When I do, I expect you to launch another attack.
It was right there in front of my face!
He's toying with us.
Shit, and with that smug-ass look on his face, too.
At this rate, the month's gonna end before we know it.
And when it does, we're gonna go
on that Impossible Mission...
...and get slaughtered.
Each and every one of us.
Monika...
At the same time,
it's too late to go back to our academies.
We're boxed in.
That Klaus punk...
With skills like his, I bet he's never even
been in a bind like ours.
I agree.
He probably can't empathize with
the worries of washouts like us at all.
That's not true.
Not at all.
He might not show it, but I think Teach has
burdens of his own he's carrying.
Lily?
We'll resume our lesson when he gets back.
Before that, though,
I have a suggestion to make as your leader.
Leader, huh?
For the record, I don't remember
ever signing off on that.
C'mon, don't be like that!
Here, have a financier with your tea.
What is that supposed to be, a bribe?
I'll have one, Leader.
Yeah, Leader, me too.
Sellouts, the lot of you.
Would you like some more tea, Monika?
There's new information regarding
your Impossible Mission.
Understood.
How are the girls holding up?
I understand you've been having
a hard time teaching them.
Nothing gets past you, does it, C?
I guess you're not in charge of the Cabinet Office's
Foreign Intelligence Office for nothing.
You're a good spy, Klaus,
but your stubbornness causes headaches
for the people around you.
You need to make sure you're doing
everything you can to assuage the girls' fears.
I don't need you to tell me that-
Oh, I think I do.
I used to be able to count on your team
to get through to you, but they're gone now.
How about this, Idiot Pupil?
If you make it back alive, I've got a new title for you:
The Greatest Spy in the World.
I'd say you will have earned it.
It's got a nice ring to it, don't you think?
Magnificent.
You don't want to flee?
Not in the slightest.
You took me in when I was an orphan
and raised me to be a spy,
and I can never thank the boss enough for hiring me.
It would be no exaggeration for me to say
that I love each and every person on this team.
I'm no expert on families,
but that's what I think of you all as.
And nothing brings me more satisfaction than
risking my life on behalf of my family.
When the hell'd you get so eloquent, Bonfire?
I'm back.
Everyone's here, I see.
Perfect.
There's something I want to talk to you all
about regarding the mission.
First of all, Lamplight isn't the first team
to attempt this Impossible Mission.
There was another one that went before us.
That team was called Inferno.
I know that name.
They're the best spy team in the Din Republic, right?
They're what every team in the nation aspires to be.
I heard that during the Great War,
they stole intel on the Imperial army
and saved the lives of hundreds
of thousands of civilians.
Wanting to join Inferno was the
reason I became a spy!
Unfortunately, Inferno is gone.
It no longer exists.
How do you know that?
Because only one person on the team survived.
And he's standing in front of you.
One year ago, I, code name Bonfire,
split off from the group and went on a solo op
per my mentor Guido's orders.
While I was gone, the rest of Inferno's members
took on an Impossible Mission.
None of them made it back alive.
Inferno was like family to me.
I wanted us to change this world,
awash in pain, together.
But now, that can never happen.
You can't be serious.
They all got wiped out?
You're saying they were
the best spy team in the nation...
...and they died on the very same mission
we'll be attempting in a month?
I apologize for frightening you.
As your instructor,
I make no excuses for my ineptitude.
That said, I had a very good reason
for choosing the seven of you.
I want you to come.
However, I'm not going to force you.
It's up to each of you to decide
if you're coming on the Impossible Mission or not.
Teach...
If you wish to flee, that right is yours.
For me, this mission is one of personal revenge.
It's an important mission,
and the fate of our nation hangs in the balance,
but that isn't reason enough for the
seven of you to risk your lives.
I'm in.
You all...
Still, to think that you were
actually a member of Inferno.
We had our suspicions,
but it hits different actually hearing you say it.
You did?
Yeah.
Y'see, Lily had this idea, so we spent the afternoon...
...investigating Heat Haze Palace's old residents.
We found traces from a couple people
of all sorts of ages and genders.
Then, after subtly asking around
at Garmouth Seminary,
we obtained some testimonies that
supported our hypothesis.
We figured that the people who lived here
must have been really important to you.
You probably hit rock bottom
when you lost the people you cared about.
Well, we were at rock bottom too.
We're not about to abandon a fellow bottom-dweller!
We're in the same hole here.
Let's climb out of it together!
But...
If I may, sir!
We all feel the same way!
You're gonna train us up real good before the mission.
Right, Bro?
Naturally.
Then let's do this!
We're all in?
I mean, hey, if the team leader says so.
Ooh! You finally signed off on it!
She was being sarcastic.
Wait, that's so mean, though!
It's okay, Leader, settle down.
Yeah, you're right.
A good leader can't let an eensy bit
of sarcasm get to her.
I can see I made the right choice picking you
as Lamplight's leader, Flower Garden Lily.
Well, yeah, obviously!
In twenty days,
we'll be heading to the Galgad Empire
to begin the Impossible Mission.
Until then, I'll continue forging
you all into proper spies.
We're going to complete this mission,
and we're all going to make it back alive.
Yes, sir!
When the time came,
Teach and the rest of us headed to where the
Impossible Mission was going to take place:
the Galgad Empire.
MISSION: Flower Garden II
It's go time.
We're going to split up and infiltrate Galgad
as two separate groups.
You're coming all the way to the Empire
to watch some plays?
Sounds like someone's living high on the hog.
Who, little old me?
The others are in the dining car right now, but-
Pardon me...
Ah, they're back.
As team leader, Lily, you're going to be
spearheading one of the groups,
while I lead up the other one.
So, you're a wood engraver?
Indeed, I am.
Wow, that's impressive.
My apprentices do me proud.
From here on out, we'll be operating separately.
Any last things you want to say to me?
I'll save them for the next time we see each other.
Until we're done here,
I'm going to avoid making contact with
anyone besides the Intel squad.
We should head out, too.
Our job is to steal a sample from a lab
on the Imperial capital's outskirts.
Yup, that's an Impossible Mission.
The Endy Laboratory, huh?
Officially, the lab belongs to a
pharmaceutical company,
but in truth...
...the Imperial army secretly uses it to conduct
cutting-edge weapons research.
Indeed.
Naturally, security there is tight.
Everything is going to hinge on how much
intel we can gather ahead of time.
The two of us on the Intel squad will start
by gathering information.
And over on the Specialist squad,
we'll use our special talents
to support the other squads, yo!
I'm counting on you, Mr. Bernard.
It says the Intel squad's used their
data to identify a key player,
and they want the Operations squad,
which is to say "us," to make contact.
Cool, then I'm gonna go do my own thing solo.
Wh-
It'll be more efficient.
This way, I'll be able to help the entire team out.
I swear, she thinks she's better than us
just 'cuz she's better than us.
What about Klaus?
Can we get him to help us out?
"I'm devoting all my efforts
to providing backup," he said.
He also said...
As far as specifics go, Intel should make
like a rose proudly blooming.
Operations should zoop-zoop-zoop around,
and the Specialist squad should watch over you
as they would a baby bird.
I want everyone giving it their all.
Yeesh, this is like some sorta sick joke.
Don't worry!
We trained our butts off for this, remember?
We've got this!
We won't let anyone call us washouts again!
Heh, easy peasy.
Wait, what's that?
A dummy.
This one here's the real one.
Klaus pulled the same trick on me once.
Looks like our training is paying off.
That guy was a drug dealer.
We should find some of the lab's staff
on the client list in here.
Hold it there, you two.
You're tourists, I take it?
Sorry, but this is a prime area for pickpockets.
I'm going to have to check your bags, just in case.
But we, uh...
What do I do?
I could put them to sleep and we could escape,
but then the cops would start looking for us...
She's clean.
Same here.
Thank you so much for cooperating.
I hope you two enjoy your trip.
Sybilla, where'd you hide the-
I didn't.
Someone stole my stolen wallet.
There's only one dude I know who
could pull off a stunt like that.
What a stand-up guy.
A magnificent one, even.
Yeah.
Still, I was scared stiff back there.
Sooner or later, our luck's gonna run out.
As things stand, I worry that some of us
won't last until the main operation...
Is that from Klaus?
No, it's from Lily.
I have the wine you ordered, sir.
Come in.
That is an excellent disguise,
but I don't see why you felt the need
to remove your mask.
I don't like to cross-dress around you, Boss.
Well, suit yourself.
What is all that?!
High-level Imperial classified information.
You collected that all on your own?
I'm impressed at how much intel
you girls have collected, too.
And in such a short time, no less.
I see we have confirmation that the sample
hasn't been moved from the Endy Laboratory.
I have another piece of news for you as well, Boss.
Our leader, Lily, was asking about us possibly holding
a party the night before the operation...
Boss?
My ears must be failing me.
Did you say "a party"?
According to her message, she wants us all
to gather and share a meal together.
Has she forgotten that we're spies in hostile territory?
That girl's shamelessness knows no bounds.
I believe she's worried about the team's fatigue levels.
And I share her concerns.
Ah, I see.
For the rest of you, this is your first real mission.
The exhaustion is starting to get to you all.
I'll make a reservation at a
trustworthy restaurant, then.
Go ahead and have your party.
Just make sure you don't get tailed.
If I may!
If it's only us, then there's a faint possibility
that something could go wrong.
Then call off the party.
But if you joined us, that problem would be resolved.
We wouldn't be in any danger.
Cheers!
Thanks for convincing him, Grete!
Sup!
Hey, you made it!
What are you three doing,
getting started all on your own?
Don't worry about it.
Klaus'll be here soon.
I did some recon on the restaurant.
If I keep watch from up here, everything will be fine.
Still, I'm not nearly as invincible as they think I am.
After all,
against him, I've never once...
What the...
Do you not understand the situation we're in?
How are you not more stressed?
Stressed?
We're stressed as hell.
But...
I mean, of course we are.
How could we not be scared?
We've been shakin' in our boots
since the minute we left Din.
Then, how?
Cuz you said you'd come today, that's how.
You're late, FYI.
That's why we figured we'd be fine.
Your strength is the one thing...
we believe in.
At least pretend to be on guard.
This is important, Klaus.
When someone lets you watch them sleep,
it's a sign of how much they trust you.
So, if anyone lets you see them like that,
make sure you do whatever it takes to protect them.
Why is it that looking at them
reminds me so much of Inferno?
Whatever the reason, though,
I feel like my resolve is firmer now.
Wait, when did he bail on us?!
And what's that?
It's from Teach.
"Change of plans."
"We talked about you going in from the east
and me from the west, but we're reversing that."
"Furthermore, I know it couldn't have been easy
having with a boss who couldn't teach or explain things."
"You have my thanks."
For real?
We never managed to make him say "I surrender"...
...but at least we got him to say "thank you".
That airhead actually thanked us.
He could have easily been doing it on a whim.
Oh, probably.
Thinking back now, though,
that might have been the moment that us
Lamplight girls and Teach truly became a team.
There it is, the Endy Laboratory.
That's where they're hiding the sample that
we need to steal back for our mission.
As you're aware, Klaus,
there is a postwar international treaty
banning the use of biological weapons.
However, it doesn't ban their development.
Or at least, that's how the imbeciles
in our army chose to interpret it.
After they went ahead and continued their research,
a Galgad spy stole one of their samples.
According to our lab boys, it should take Galgad
a year to analyze the compound.
However, we've received word from one of our
collaborators in their capital, Darton,
that the Imperial research efforts are
proceeding faster than anticipated.
At this rate...
...the casualty count could well reach into the millions.
The Empire has no qualms about getting
innocent civilians caught up in their assassinations.
I need you and the girls to retrieve that bioweapon.
It's a killer virus, and its name...
...is Abyss Doll.